Let's look in detail how he got is implemented in this session.
We will explore the sequence of steps to activate the key guard security window.
Here's a sequence diagram that shows the sequence of steps to activate the key security window the physical
key input is intercepted by the input dispatcher and is sent to foreign window manager, which in turn
sends to guard service and the key guard service calls the old system ready method in system UIC Guard
View Mediator Class So as can be seen from this sequence diagram, the user raises the physicality of
the Android device, so the Android device propagates a key plus event to its input.
DISPATCHER The input dispatcher sends a message to activate the key guard to warn Window Manager, plus
the phone window manager class.
After doing some processing sends a message to activate, he got security window rookie guard service.
Then the key guard service calls the old system ready method of Gegard View mediator.
And this process happens through Binder IPCA Binder in the process communication.
So the Binder IPC is used because the key guard service is in a completely different process, and the
system UI is again and another process to communicate with these two processes.
We need binding IPC in this session.
We are focusing on the key guard system UI related modules.
Now let us look deeper into what's happening within the system UI.
He got modules.
Here's a sequence diagram that shows the classes and methods involved in displaying key keycard security
window to the user, as can be seen.
The keycard view mediator is the class that triggers the process within System UI.
So as we saw in the last second diagram, the Kiger View mediator gets the status update from the key
guard Sahrawis through Binder IPC.
So now let's see what's happening within the system UI classes.
So once the system UI gets to control, the old system ready method calls the handle system ready method
and the handle system ready method course new key guard lock, which in turn calls show law and show
locked in turn calls.
Handler Show Method, which is part of Status Bar in Dark View Manager and within legal view manager
he calls Show Method and the SHA method in turn calls Cho Bouncer or Key Guard Method and the show bouncer.
Ortega's method uses the bouncer object inbound setup, which is basically an object of Gegard Bouncer
class, and it goes to prepare them at the proper method in turn uses empty guard view object and calls
show primary security screen method within Gegard Host View and the key guard host view.
Finally, calls the show primary security screen method, which in turn uses the key guard security
container object and calls method show primary security screen.
The key guard security container goes to show security screen method, and it finally displays the security
screen to the end user.
So this was a short overview about the sequence of methods and the classes involved in this process.
In the next section, we will look into the code and dig this in detail.